Miller, Frank, Papers /4311
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Industrial and Labor Relations Review (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Who is Really Better at Math (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Late Math Handouts (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Segment Three. Explanations Handouts (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Sex and the Personnel Manager (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Girls at Puberty. Science Review, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- The Female Labor Force, 1870-1989 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- ILR 9765. Current Working Admin Notes, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Course Outline. ILR 9765 Part One (Box 4, Folder 62)
- JTPA Material (Box 4, Folder 63)
- CETA of 1973 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Comprehensive Employment and Training Act of 1973 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Assorted Annotated Articles (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Interviewing Notes and Reprints (Box 4, Folder 67)
- "The Book" (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Mentalistic Phenomena: Article re (Box 4, Folder 69)
- The Personnel Dilemma: Professional or Not (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Why I'm Professionalizing (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Personnel Research Contributions. US Universities (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Sex and the Personnel Manager (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Review: On the Shop Floor: Two Studies of Workshop Organization and Output (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Situational Interactions (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Resistentialism (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Incentive Article. Carbons (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Power Tactics (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Book (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Case Studies in the Delivery of Vocational Rehabilitation Services: Conceptual and Empirical Dimensions, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Section I. Prepared by William h. Button, PhD and Leslie J Miller, MA
- Service Feasibility Study: Taking the Professional Pulse, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Section II. Prepared by Frank B. Miller, PhD
- History of Personnel (manuscript draft) (Box 5, Folder 3)
- The Human Population by Edward S. Deevey, Jr., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- George Price - 1964 Rochester Project (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Transparencies for classroom instruction (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Occupational Prestige, 1962-1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Contains journal articles, data sets, and notes on this topic
- Reports on grant work regarding the occupational stereotypes of industry executives, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Includes interim reports, data sets, and research designs.
- ILR 360 - coursework, 1976-1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Class notes, lessons plans, readings for class taught by Frank Miller in 1984
- Historical sources of personnel work (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Publications by Frank Miller and Mary Ann Coghill
- Occupational Status Research: Social Consensus Measure. Survey instrument and data sets, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Tracking social placement based on occupation and gender
- Occupational Status Research: Social Consensus Measure, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Correspondence, survey instruments, and student work on occupation as indicator of social standing with regard to gender
- Occupational Status Research: Social Consensus Measure. Coding Key for Appendix, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Semantic Differential Personnel (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Racism and Sexism in Corporate America, Fernandez book report materials (Box 5, Folder 15)
- "Are IQ tests intelligent?" by Raymond Bernard Cattell, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Published articles by Frank Miller (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Components - verbal terms (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Frank Miller's Art File (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Drawings by Professor Miller
- "Development of Industrial Relations in the United States" by Bryce M. Stewart, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Student papers from ILR 660, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  6 papers by three students
- Research notes (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Memorial paperweight for ILR Building dedication, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Green stone paperweight with engraving of new ILR building. Text reads: "School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Building Dedication, April 17, 1998"